{
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "1. What is the capital city of Sri Lanka?",
        "answers": ["Colombo", "Kandy", "Galle", "Jaffna"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "2. Which ocean surrounds Sri Lanka?",
        "answers": [
          "Indian Ocean",
          "Pacific Ocean",
          "Atlantic Ocean",
          "Arctic Ocean"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "3. What is the official language of Sri Lanka?",
        "answers": ["English", "Malay", "Sinhala", "Tamil"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2
      },
      {
        "question": "4. Which planet is known as the Red Planet?",
        "answers": ["Venus", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "5. In which year did the Titanic sink?",
        "answers": ["1912", "1920", "1905", "1935"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "6. Who painted the Mona Lisa?",
        "answers": [
          "Vincent van Gogh",
          "Leonardo da Vinci",
          "Pablo Picasso",
          "Claude Monet"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "7. What is the largest mammal on Earth?",
        "answers": ["Elephant", "Blue Whale", "Giraffe", "Hippopotamus"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
      },
      {
        "question": "8. Which element has the chemical symbol O?",
        "answers": ["Oxygen", "Gold", "Iron", "Carbon"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "9. Who is the author of To Kill a Mockingbird?",
        "answers": [
          "Harper Lee",
          "J.K. Rowling",
          "George Orwell",
          "Ernest Hemingway"
        ],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
      },
      {
        "question": "10. What is the capital of Japan?",
        "answers": ["Beijing", "Seoul", "Tokyo", "Bangkok"],
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2
      }
    ]
  }
  